<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:04:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/thoughts/2026/2026-01-21-untitled-433479/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/thoughts/2026/2026-01-21-untitled-433479/</guid>
      <description>i feel guilty, its two days and I still havent started my journey. Man!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Meditation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/my-experience-with-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:10:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/blog/my-experience-with-meditation/</guid>
      <description>The motivation for meditation did not come from a book or a youtube video, it came from within me, my desire to get rid of those dreams I was getting so much. Earlier I would get those vivid dreams sometimes and they would be lucid sometimes, but after I left home and started living on my own, they started to become very frequent. I do not think I am less happy now that I am out of my house, but it definitely triggered something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in Review - 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/year-in-review-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/blog/year-in-review-2025/</guid>
      <description>So after trying to write for last two years, I think I am going to finish writing this year. Lets tackle different aspects of my life one by one.&#xA;Studies I finished my graduation this year on July-August. My college life is finally over, trying to take entry into work life and leave this student life behind. I do not plan on higher studies. Only places that I need higher degrees is in teaching related jobs, and I do not plan on doing those, trying to avoid it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achievements in College Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/blog/achievements-in-college-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 23:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/blog/achievements-in-college-life/</guid>
      <description>Here is the list of achievements in my college life(2022-25). Both positive and negative.&#xA;Positive Achievements Rank second in college exam. Get paid for computer related work. Make friends with all the classmates. Become Class Monitor. Become first in something. Go out with a girl. Get gifts from someone for helping him/her. Become Close with someone. Become close with my crush. Influence whole class&amp;rsquo;s descision. Show my computer skill. Spend teacher&amp;rsquo;s day/farewell in other&amp;rsquo;s dept.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
