<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guide on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guide on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:54:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Use AI in Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-i-use-ai-in-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-i-use-ai-in-studies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unlike most Tech youtubers i do not think AI is useless. It is far from being useless. I think these techtubers are so confined to their own little worlds that they lack the imagination of what can be done in other areas of life.  Specially for a low skilled person like me it has been useful so far for me. From the last year I have been using ai in different parts of my life. I want to talk about how I have integrated AI in my studies in this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Microblogging Website Using Hugo &amp; Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 19:30:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;check-a-live-version&#34;&gt;Check a live version:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out live version of the website that I made.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://status.blackpiratex.com/&#34;&gt;https://status.blackpiratex.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Blogs are great if you want to write something that is atleast one paragraph. But for those one line thoughts that comes to your mind, which you want to share with the world or want to write it down, &amp;lsquo;cause most likely you would not remember it in future, microblogging is the way to go. If you are not familier with this term, it means twitter like platform, where you can make posts but those would be not more than a paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Website on Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 17:43:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration&#34;&gt;Inspiration:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as I can remember, I came to know about &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; from some personal blogs, which I have found through &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.ycombinator.com&#34;&gt;Hacker News&lt;/a&gt;. Before this I was coding everything manually for each blog post. (you can see examples of those &lt;a href=&#34;https://blackpiratex.com/blog&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.) And yes it was tedious. I noticed that I spent most of my time making the html and css, instead of writting the actual content. Also the friction involed in getting my post published made me less likely to post. Clearly something needs to change. I started playing with Hugo. And With little bit of research and guides form Youtube, I started learning about it. Decided that I would make my blog separate from my website, that way it would be easier to manage. I initially used &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;premade themes by community&lt;/a&gt; for my website. Themes usually decide how your website will look. (It&amp;rsquo;s just like wordpress themes.) I also created another seprate website on a subdomain for my &lt;a href=&#34;https://gallery.blackpiratex.com&#34;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt; website. Premade themes are very good nontheless, but they are not suitable for me. I do not want to use any JS if possible. So I needed to create my own theme. After reading on the Hugo Documentation and taking help from &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ZFL09qhKi5I/&#34;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&#34;https://lukesmith.xyz&#34;&gt;Luke Smith&lt;/a&gt;, I created my own theme. It is going to be a simple theme, but functional and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
