<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dream on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41373/tags/dream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dream on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41373/tags/dream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dream: Meeting Someone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-meeting-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-meeting-someone/</guid>
      <description>I went to see something by my college road. But in the way we met a weird person. It looked like a mentally unstable person. We were teasing him. He started following us. Then halfway through the journey, there was a shop type 2 story building. He quickly changed and transformed into a girl. Yep, he was trans. He kept following us. Now we are in the bhamuria Road, but I am actually going to the sammilani college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: A Beautiful Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-beautiful-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-beautiful-garden/</guid>
      <description>I was someone else. Probably my brother and saw myself waiting in a hall. It was our college exam and somehow I forgot to do form fillup.&#xA;The me, in someone else&amp;rsquo;s body went to a hotel, but overheard the owner giving instructions to raise the prices for the students who came to give exam. So I left. The exam centre was right beside Ganga. So I reached one of the Gangas ghat, and when I entered the exam centre again it was the hall where all people who were not eligible was sitting and someone was instructing them to go with with to some office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: A Movie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-movie/</guid>
      <description>Main character me, brother and another guy. Who is black.&#xA;I was cleaning a toilet because it was overflowing. That made vomit reflex and woke me up. Took me at least 3-4 tries to finish cleaning&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s another scene where 3 of us were walking at the side of a road/railway. Suddenly a tank came and blocked the whole road. Veichles came fast and crashed into it. 2nd vehicle broke the tank itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: First Aeroplane Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-first-aeroplane-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-first-aeroplane-experience/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt this after drinking coffee.&#xA;I had my first experience of riding an aeroplane. It was riding very low and the windows were not glass. It was like a toy and it was fun.&#xA;Then in train Pabitra had a bhai who was not found. He said his brother came with us but he was not sure if actially. He said that he would say that he is dead and instructed us to make a fake dead body to show in case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream about painting a house and trying different food dishes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-about-painting-a-house-and-trying-different-food-dishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-about-painting-a-house-and-trying-different-food-dishes/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt this on 9th Jan, 2025. I drank coffee that day.&#xA;I dreamt that I was with mom and we were trying dishes&#xA;There was a girl who was ironing some fabric that was supposed to be edible. She burnt some fabric and also in the process her sweater. Her dad took it from her and started doing it. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it tasted becase we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to taste it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Entry #1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-entry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-entry-1/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt again.&#xA;This time I was running away from people of an universe of exact same people of this universe. Actually it was parallel universe, everything is exact copy.&#xA;A bean like thing has corrupted mind of almost all the people of that parallel universe and made everyone evil.I wasn&amp;rsquo;t effected by those beans for some reason. But I had no idea that I was not effected. At first there were no beans, then suddenly beans were everywhere, like it was raining beans.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
