<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:19:40 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:19:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/credits/</guid>
      <description> Thanks Ornella for reporting grammertical and spelling mistakes. Few gifs on the footer were taken from https://lime360.neocities.org and the rest were taken from yesterweb discord server. Also thanks to countless searches on google/duckduckgo. W3schools and MDN Web docs helped me to build this website from scratch. Thanks to them too. Sam for keeping me inspired. The table at the front page was shamelessly stolen from Bugswriter. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookmarks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 15:55:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>Here are some links that I find are cool.&#xA;Websites that I have made: https://blackpiratex.com https://blog.blackpiratex.com https://status.blackpiratex.com https://notes.blackpiratex.com https://quotes.blackpiratex.com https://sudipx.in https://blackpirate.be.eu.org https://sambot.blackpiratex.com/ (obselete) https://smandalofficial.zohosites.com (offline - clicking on it will show archived version) Friends https://saqibmir1.github.io/ Cool Web 1.0 Websites That I Like: https://sadgrl.online https://bugswriter.com https://cinni.net/ Favourite Blogs https://www.vipshek.com/blog/ https://www.izzy.co/blog.html https://heather-buchel.com/ https://www.arp242.net/ Tools https://willus.com/k2pdfopt/download/ - Convert PDF files to readable on kindle. https://www.goatcounter.com/ - Open Source and free analytics for website Opensource Android Apps This list contains opensource apps that I have used over the years which are not very well known.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 16:45:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email - If you want to reach me quickly, this is best option. I would appreciate it if you do not send spam.&#xA;Discord - I am online here quite often. Feel free to DM me here.&#xA;Github - My github account. Nothing interesting to see, just bunch of forks.&#xA;Spotify - My Spotify account.&#xA;last.fm - My last.fm profile. Get a overview of my music taste. Maybe our music taste is similar?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 16:24:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description> Hey, stranger on the internet. Hope you&#39;re doing well. I&#39;m Sudip. This is a personal place for me on the internet. This is a also a place for me to experiment all the new things I learn about web developmet. I am currently studying zoology. Making website is one of my hobbies. And I love ducks and cats. Here is a cute duck for you to enjoy! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>My list of Hobbies Computer I like almost everything computer related, may that be hardware or software. I like coding, although nowadays I do not get much time to do it. As I am relatively busy with college.&#xA;List of favourite things to do in computer learn to code. make my website. rice my desktop. try new linux distribution inside virtualbox or hardware. hardening softwares for privacy and security (to the point where it breaks the program).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/music/</guid>
      <description>Music In all possible mood, I listen to music. If you want a real time data about what music I listen to, check out my last.fm profile.&#xA;My Top favourite Artist: </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
