<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:31:47 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simplelogin - Best Way to Manage Your Emails</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/simplelogin-best-way-to-manage-your-emails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:31:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/simplelogin-best-way-to-manage-your-emails/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SimpleLogin is a email aliasing service. Which basically means you can create as many emails as you want* and all those emails would land on single inbox. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using SimpleLogin for over a year now. Here&amp;rsquo;s my evaluation of the service. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-use-case&#34;&gt;My Use Case&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As someone who cares about privacy, and had personal emails leaked in data breach previously, I treat emails just like my passwords. I don&amp;rsquo;t want fifty different companies to know my email address just so they can send me marketing emails. Also if you use same email everywhere its pretty easy to stalk you online. Anyone who has your email address would be able to know if you use (or have account) certain website. I don&amp;rsquo;t want others to know which website I visit or which website I have an&#xA;account. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Degoogled Phone Isn&#39;t as Hard as You Might Think</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:27:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-degoogled-phone&#34;&gt;What is a degoogled phone?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vanilla Android is &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.blackpiratex.com/tags/FOSS/&#34;&gt;FOSS&lt;/a&gt; (Free and OpenSource Software), but the android that you get preinstalled in most phones isn&amp;rsquo;t completely FOSS. It has a blackbox, which is called Google Play Services. A lot of android apps and all google apps relies on this. Sure it provides features like instant notification, but privacy is a nightmare. Degoogling a phone means removing this blackbox, by installing a different flavour of Android which doesn&amp;rsquo;t ship with Google Play Services by default.  LineageOs is a popular example.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
