<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41373/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:17:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41373/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Has Fake Reviews on Playstore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/whatsapp-has-fake-reviews-on-playstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:50:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/whatsapp-has-fake-reviews-on-playstore/</guid>
      <description>I was reading reviews for Whatsapp on playstore and came to see this:&#xA;There is more:&#xA;And more:&#xA;This one too:&#xA;I am sure if you search, more will come. I wonder who&amp;rsquo;s doing these!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Microblogging Website Using Hugo &amp; Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 19:30:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</guid>
      <description>Check a live version: Check out live version of the website that I made. https://status.blackpiratex.com/&#xA;Blogs are great if you want to write something that is atleast one paragraph. But for those one line thoughts that comes to your mind, which you want to share with the world or want to write it down, &amp;lsquo;cause most likely you would not remember it in future, microblogging is the way to go. If you are not familier with this term, it means twitter like platform, where you can make posts but those would be not more than a paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Website on Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 17:43:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration: As far as I can remember, I came to know about Hugo from some personal blogs, which I have found through Hacker News. Before this I was coding everything manually for each blog post. (you can see examples of those here.) And yes it was tedious. I noticed that I spent most of my time making the html and css, instead of writting the actual content. Also the friction involed in getting my post published made me less likely to post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Doesn&#39;t Like Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/fedora-doesnt-like-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:54:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/fedora-doesnt-like-me/</guid>
      <description>After listening lots of good things about fedora, I wanted to give it a try. I was previously using Archcraft, but recently it started to give me few errors. Dolphin won&amp;rsquo;t start for some reason. Same problem with OBS Studio also. I can live without dolphin, but needed obs studio. I got an workaround and used ffmpeg to record screen, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as good as obs studio. So I decided to distro-hop like any rational person would (I hope).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Degoogled Phone Isn&#39;t as Hard as You Might Think</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:27:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</guid>
      <description>What is a degoogled phone? Vanilla Android is FOSS (Free and OpenSource Software), but the android that you get preinstalled in most phones isn&amp;rsquo;t completely FOSS. It has a blackbox, which is called Google Play Services. A lot of android apps and all google apps relies on this. Sure it provides features like instant notification, but privacy is a nightmare. Degoogling a phone means removing this blackbox, by installing a different flavour of Android which doesn&amp;rsquo;t ship with Google Play Services by default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Search for Perfect Daily Journal App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/in-search-for-perfect-daily-journal-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:08:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/in-search-for-perfect-daily-journal-app/</guid>
      <description>To be considered a viable app for my Daily Journal needs it must have following charateristics.&#xA;Decent UI Either end to end encrypted if the app is cloud based or data stays locally. Cross platform. Including Linux. Easy way to export for personal backups. Free Because of lack of privacy at my home, I had moved away from physical pen and paper diaries and moved completely to digital. It&amp;rsquo;s much easier to hide something online than trying to hide at my home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Various Password Managers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-various-password-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 18:53:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-various-password-managers/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the years i have used many password managers. One of the biggest reasons I started using a password manager is not because of the security but rather I wanted a quick way to type my passwords. Also its easy for me to loose track of the websites I have signed up for. Now you may ask why I didn&amp;rsquo;t use something like password manager built in most modern web browser?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
