<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on BlackPirateX</title>
    <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on BlackPirateX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:10:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:41373/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Meditation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:10:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-meditation/</guid>
      <description>The motivation for meditation did not come from a book or a youtube video, it came from within me, my desire to get rid of those dreams I was getting so much. Earlier I would get those vivid dreams sometimes and they would be lucid sometimes, but after I left home and started living on my own, they started to become very frequent. I do not think I am less happy now that I am out of my house, but it definitely triggered something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Use AI in Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/how-i-use-ai-in-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 22:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/how-i-use-ai-in-studies/</guid>
      <description>Unlike most Tech youtubers i do not think AI is useless. It is far from being useless. I think these techtubers are so confined to their own little worlds that they lack the imagination of what can be done in other areas of life. Specially for a low skilled person like me it has been useful so far for me. From the last year I have been using ai in different parts of my life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in Review - 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/year-in-review-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/year-in-review-2025/</guid>
      <description>So after trying to write for last two years, I think I am going to finish writing this year. Lets tackle different aspects of my life one by one.&#xA;Studies I finished my graduation this year on July-August. My college life is finally over, trying to take entry into work life and leave this student life behind. I do not plan on higher studies. Only places that I need higher degrees is in teaching related jobs, and I do not plan on doing those, trying to avoid it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: Meeting Someone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-meeting-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-meeting-someone/</guid>
      <description>I went to see something by my college road. But in the way we met a weird person. It looked like a mentally unstable person. We were teasing him. He started following us. Then halfway through the journey, there was a shop type 2 story building. He quickly changed and transformed into a girl. Yep, he was trans. He kept following us. Now we are in the bhamuria Road, but I am actually going to the sammilani college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranchi Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/ranchi-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/ranchi-experience/</guid>
      <description>Background This journey was because of NTPC (railway) exam, that happened on 14th August. I went there on 13th and came back home on 15th.&#xA;Things that I noticed are different. People in Jharkhand eats a lot of Samosa. Specially on train. The price is 10/piece. I bought 4 at Hatia Railway Station.&#xA;Female Hawkers, There are significant number of female hawkers, way more than that i see in West Bengal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achievements in College Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/achievements-in-college-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 23:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/achievements-in-college-life/</guid>
      <description>Here is the list of achievements in my college life(2022-25). Both positive and negative.&#xA;Positive Achievements Rank second in college exam. Get paid for computer related work. Make friends with all the classmates. Become Class Monitor. Become first in something. Go out with a girl. Get gifts from someone for helping him/her. Become Close with someone. Become close with my crush. Influence whole class&amp;rsquo;s descision. Show my computer skill. Spend teacher&amp;rsquo;s day/farewell in other&amp;rsquo;s dept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: A Beautiful Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-beautiful-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-beautiful-garden/</guid>
      <description>I was someone else. Probably my brother and saw myself waiting in a hall. It was our college exam and somehow I forgot to do form fillup.&#xA;The me, in someone else&amp;rsquo;s body went to a hotel, but overheard the owner giving instructions to raise the prices for the students who came to give exam. So I left. The exam centre was right beside Ganga. So I reached one of the Gangas ghat, and when I entered the exam centre again it was the hall where all people who were not eligible was sitting and someone was instructing them to go with with to some office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: A Movie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-a-movie/</guid>
      <description>Main character me, brother and another guy. Who is black.&#xA;I was cleaning a toilet because it was overflowing. That made vomit reflex and woke me up. Took me at least 3-4 tries to finish cleaning&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s another scene where 3 of us were walking at the side of a road/railway. Suddenly a tank came and blocked the whole road. Veichles came fast and crashed into it. 2nd vehicle broke the tank itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream: First Aeroplane Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-first-aeroplane-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-first-aeroplane-experience/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt this after drinking coffee.&#xA;I had my first experience of riding an aeroplane. It was riding very low and the windows were not glass. It was like a toy and it was fun.&#xA;Then in train Pabitra had a bhai who was not found. He said his brother came with us but he was not sure if actially. He said that he would say that he is dead and instructed us to make a fake dead body to show in case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream about painting a house and trying different food dishes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-about-painting-a-house-and-trying-different-food-dishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-about-painting-a-house-and-trying-different-food-dishes/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt this on 9th Jan, 2025. I drank coffee that day.&#xA;I dreamt that I was with mom and we were trying dishes&#xA;There was a girl who was ironing some fabric that was supposed to be edible. She burnt some fabric and also in the process her sweater. Her dad took it from her and started doing it. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it tasted becase we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to taste it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I get Daily News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/how-i-get-daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 23:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/how-i-get-daily-news/</guid>
      <description>In this post I would discuss how I read news on my kindle, benefit of my method and how you can replicate this method by yourself.&#xA;How to Replicate Prerequisites: A smartphone with Termux and Anlinux installed. There must be at least 2 GB of storage free. Patience Time on your hand. Installing a Linux distro on termux Open the an Linux app and on the dashboard choose Fedora and click ok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hyprland Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/the-hyprland-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 23:55:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/the-hyprland-experience/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Arch Linux with Hyprland. Initially I started using because of the cool animation it has. And stayed with it since.&#xA;Look and Feel Hyprland excels at it. Animations are super smooth and eyecatchy.I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily care for eye candy features, but this time made an exception. The default look is actually pretty good. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to do much ricing to get it look sexy.&#xA;A picture of my Hyprland setup, taken by phone, because I cannot figure out how to take screenshot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Entry #1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-entry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/dream-entry-1/</guid>
      <description>I dreamt again.&#xA;This time I was running away from people of an universe of exact same people of this universe. Actually it was parallel universe, everything is exact copy.&#xA;A bean like thing has corrupted mind of almost all the people of that parallel universe and made everyone evil.I wasn&amp;rsquo;t effected by those beans for some reason. But I had no idea that I was not effected. At first there were no beans, then suddenly beans were everywhere, like it was raining beans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Fountain Pen Collection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-fountain-pen-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 20:43:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-fountain-pen-collection/</guid>
      <description>I like pens. If you ask my family they would tell you how much money I have spent (ahem, wasted) on pens. I used almost all type of pens there is, that is if they are available for purchase in India. My recent obsession is fountain pens. I love them. A good fountain pen writes miles better than any other kind of pen. But they are expensive. Like very expensive. But most the fountain pens are made so that they can be used for a very long time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming on Spotify vs Using Mp3s</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/streaming-on-spotify-vs-using-mp3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:52:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/streaming-on-spotify-vs-using-mp3s/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: here by mp3 I am referring to any playable music file, with any extension.&#xA;For most people Spotify is great, or at least it is better than managing your own mp3s like in the old days. But there are few things that I absolutely hate, which made me switch to MP3.&#xA;Things that pisses me off about Spotify: Podcasts - I know a lot of people who listens to podcast through Spotify, but I hate it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Has Fake Reviews on Playstore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/whatsapp-has-fake-reviews-on-playstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:50:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/whatsapp-has-fake-reviews-on-playstore/</guid>
      <description>I was reading reviews for Whatsapp on playstore and came to see this:&#xA;There is more:&#xA;And more:&#xA;This one too:&#xA;I am sure if you search, more will come. I wonder who&amp;rsquo;s doing these!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Microblogging Website Using Hugo &amp; Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 19:30:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/making-microblogging-website-using-hugo-and-netlify/</guid>
      <description>Check a live version: Check out live version of the website that I made. https://status.blackpiratex.com/&#xA;Blogs are great if you want to write something that is atleast one paragraph. But for those one line thoughts that comes to your mind, which you want to share with the world or want to write it down, &amp;lsquo;cause most likely you would not remember it in future, microblogging is the way to go. If you are not familier with this term, it means twitter like platform, where you can make posts but those would be not more than a paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up My Website on Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 17:43:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/setting-up-my-website-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration: As far as I can remember, I came to know about Hugo from some personal blogs, which I have found through Hacker News. Before this I was coding everything manually for each blog post. (you can see examples of those here.) And yes it was tedious. I noticed that I spent most of my time making the html and css, instead of writting the actual content. Also the friction involed in getting my post published made me less likely to post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Update #1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/website-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 17:46:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/website-update-1/</guid>
      <description>If you have visited my this blog before,(and can remember it) you can clearly see the difference. This blog is now simpler. I like it. Hope you like it too. As I am going to get busy with my life, I hope I would stick with this theme for very long.&#xA;How this website is made I use Hugo for creating this website. Hugo is great. I am loving it. Earlier also I was using Hugo, but that time I didn&amp;rsquo;t know much about it, so I used a ready made theme for my website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Doesn&#39;t Like Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/fedora-doesnt-like-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:54:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/fedora-doesnt-like-me/</guid>
      <description>After listening lots of good things about fedora, I wanted to give it a try. I was previously using Archcraft, but recently it started to give me few errors. Dolphin won&amp;rsquo;t start for some reason. Same problem with OBS Studio also. I can live without dolphin, but needed obs studio. I got an workaround and used ffmpeg to record screen, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as good as obs studio. So I decided to distro-hop like any rational person would (I hope).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplelogin - Best Way to Manage Your Emails</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/simplelogin-best-way-to-manage-your-emails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:31:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/simplelogin-best-way-to-manage-your-emails/</guid>
      <description>SimpleLogin is a email aliasing service. Which basically means you can create as many emails as you want* and all those emails would land on single inbox. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using SimpleLogin for over a year now. Here&amp;rsquo;s my evaluation of the service. My Use Case As someone who cares about privacy, and had personal emails leaked in data breach previously, I treat emails just like my passwords. I don&amp;rsquo;t want fifty different companies to know my email address just so they can send me marketing emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Degoogled Phone Isn&#39;t as Hard as You Might Think</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:27:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/using-degoogled-phone-isnt-as-hard-as-you-might-think/</guid>
      <description>What is a degoogled phone? Vanilla Android is FOSS (Free and OpenSource Software), but the android that you get preinstalled in most phones isn&amp;rsquo;t completely FOSS. It has a blackbox, which is called Google Play Services. A lot of android apps and all google apps relies on this. Sure it provides features like instant notification, but privacy is a nightmare. Degoogling a phone means removing this blackbox, by installing a different flavour of Android which doesn&amp;rsquo;t ship with Google Play Services by default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Search for Perfect Daily Journal App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/in-search-for-perfect-daily-journal-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:08:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/in-search-for-perfect-daily-journal-app/</guid>
      <description>To be considered a viable app for my Daily Journal needs it must have following charateristics.&#xA;Decent UI Either end to end encrypted if the app is cloud based or data stays locally. Cross platform. Including Linux. Easy way to export for personal backups. Free Because of lack of privacy at my home, I had moved away from physical pen and paper diaries and moved completely to digital. It&amp;rsquo;s much easier to hide something online than trying to hide at my home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Journaling Is Better Than Physical Journaling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/digital-journaling-is-better-than-physical-journaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:18:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/digital-journaling-is-better-than-physical-journaling/</guid>
      <description>Better Privacy A daily journal is probably going to be one of the most private thing in your life. Because I know for a fact that, doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how close you are to me I&amp;rsquo;m never going to share my journal with anyone but me. If you are able to write digitally right way then it is very much possible to have greater privacy than that you&amp;rsquo;d get in physical journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Love Tiling Window Manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/why-i-love-wm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:13:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/why-i-love-wm/</guid>
      <description>Tiling Window Manager is alternative to using full blown desktop environment. More info on ArchWiki&#xA;I have recently started using WM, first i3 now on openbox. And absolutely love it.&#xA;If you are someone who is used to use normal desktop environment like gnome, kde, xfce or any other DE (Desktop Environment), I&amp;rsquo;d suggest to try out WM.You can start with anyone of those window manager you&amp;rsquo;re comfortable with. Setting up wm is easy on fresh arch install so it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a barrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Various Password Managers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-various-password-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 18:53:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/my-experience-with-various-password-managers/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the years i have used many password managers. One of the biggest reasons I started using a password manager is not because of the security but rather I wanted a quick way to type my passwords. Also its easy for me to loose track of the websites I have signed up for. Now you may ask why I didn&amp;rsquo;t use something like password manager built in most modern web browser?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nextdns Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:41373/blog/nextdns-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 14:35:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:41373/blog/nextdns-review/</guid>
      <description>What is DNS? The Domain Name System is a hierarchical and decentralized naming system for computers, services, or other resources connected to the Internet or a private network. It associates various information with domain names assigned to each of the participating entities.&#xA;What is NextDNS? NextDNS is a dns service which lets you block sites at dns level. That means it can block ads and trackers. Which is the main selling point of this service.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
